

704.609.4012 reneecreative.com reneebrowncreative@gmail.com

I'm a Creative Professional with a passion for forward thinking design. I have dabbled in web and print for a little over five years. I love meeting new people and when not designing, I can be found taking an abundance of pictures, due to my second love: photography.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Brown Communications Art Director

Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada Feb 2012 - Nov 2013

Brainstorm, conceive, and develop advertising and marketing campaigns for a variety of clients, including fortune 500 companies. Designed print and web campaigns and oversaw production in all media involved. Helped direct photo shoots and worked directly with the Account Supervisor and Creative Director during production. Worked hands on and in collaboration with web designers, and print designers, on all media as needed.

Noblet Design Group Graphic Designer

Regina, Saskatchewan, Canada Mar 2010 - Sep 2010

Designed and developed content for the Web and for printed materials. Clients included SIAST, The Arts, Inches-A-Weigh, and Creative Kids.

Thondo Communications **Junior Web Designer**

Atlanta, GA, USA Apr 2009 – Mar 2010

Designed and developed content for a variety of electronic media, including Web sites (front end & back end), direct mail, web, banner ads, and Web promotional materials. Designed a wide range of printed materials and branding identities for English and Italian clients.

Mystique Creative Graphic Designer Toronto, Ontario, Canada Aug 2008 – Jan 2009

Worked directly with clients to create and design identities, posters, annual reports, magazine and newspaper layouts and invitations. Clients included Sony BMG, IBM, World Wildlife Fund, and the Kidney Foundation.

EDUCATION

Appalachian State University B/A in Art with Graphic Design

Aug 2003 – May 2008

Boone, NC, USA